beatthatquote.com 2014-06-29

# BeatThatQuote.com

### OUR TERMS OF USE

These terms and conditions govern the use you may make of our website, www.beatthatquote.com (the "website"). Please read these terms carefully before you start using our website. By using this Website you are accepting these terms and conditions.

You must NOT use our website if:

  * You do not agree to these terms and conditions; or
  * You are under 18 (or under 17 in the case of motor insurance or under 16 in case of moped insurance); or
  * You are not eligible for the financial products listed on the website.

### INFORMATION ABOUT US AND OUR WEBSITE

BeatThatQuote.com is a website operated by BeatThatQuote.com Limited ("we", "us" and "our"). We are a limited company registered in England and Wales with number 05346120 and the following registered address:

BeatthatQuote.com Ltd  
5 New Street Square  
London  
EC4A 3TW

We are an appointed representative of Best Value Financial Services Limited that is authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA). Its Financial Services Register number is FRN 449766, you can check this on the Financial Services Register by visiting the FCA's website [www.fca.org.uk/firms/systems-reporting/register](http://www.fca.org.uk/firms/systems-reporting/register)or by contacting the FCA on 0800 111 6768.

### OUR SERVICES

We offer a number of different products and services on our website. This section applies to all products and services on our website.

Our service allows you to either compare various insurance, financial and other products or to be introduced to a broker who may be able to help with your enquiry. Our service is free for you to use. We receive commission and fees from certain product or service providers who we refer you to.

Nothing in our website is, or will be deemed to constitute, financial, investment or other advice or a recommendation or endorsement by us. The material we provide on our website is for your general information purposes only and you should not rely on it. It is your sole decision whether to obtain any product or service via our website and your sole responsibility to check the suitability, adequacy and appropriateness of the product or service that is of interest to you. In this respect, you should consider seeking independent professional advice before you obtain any product or service via our website.

There are some specific things that you also need to know about some of the products services on our website before you can access or use them. These things relate to Insurance Products and Services. If you click on these links, you will be taken to these additional terms and conditions. Otherwise, they can be found at the bottom of these terms and conditions under the heading INFORMATION ABOUT SPECIFIC PRODUCTS OR SERVICES ON OUR WEBSITE. As with the rest of these terms and conditions, if you do not agree with any of the additional product specific terms, do not use this website.

### YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF OUR WEBSITE AND CONTENT

You may only use our website for personal purposes and you must not use this website:

  * For commercial purposes.
  * For any fraudulent or illegal purpose.
  * On behalf of someone else such as to create, check, modify or amend another person's record or enquiry.
  * To harm, intimidate or harass, embarrass or defame another person, or in a way that invades another person's privacy.
  * To post any obscene or offensive material (as determined by us).
  * To tamper with, modify, reverse engineer or amend any part of this website.
  * In a way that interferes with our communications and technical systems (as determined by us).
  * Using any 'screen scraping' or automated software, process, program, system robot, web crawler, spider, data mining or trawler.

### OUR WEBSITE AVAILABILITY

We will always try to provide you with uninterrupted access to our website, but we cannot make any promises about this and may terminate, suspend or restrict your access to our website at any time if this is required for security, legal or reasons we determine. 

### CHANGES TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS

We may modify these terms or any additional terms that apply to a service to, for example, reflect changes to the law or changes to our services. You should look at the terms regularly. We’ll post notice of modifications to these terms on this page. Changes will not apply retrospectively and will become effective no earlier than fourteen days after they are posted. However, changes addressing new functions for a service or changes made for legal reasons will be effective immediately. If you do not agree to the modified terms for our services, you should discontinue your use of the services. Your continued use of our services following modification of the terms demonstrates acceptance of the modified terms.

### INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS

The words 'Beat That Quote' and the BeatThatQuote.com logo are our trademarks. All other logos, trademarks and material we display on our website along with the software, know how and processes we use to run our website belong to BeatThatQuote.com Ltd or our licensors. This means all copyright, design rights, patents, inventions, trading names, service marks and trademarks, logos, domain names, moral rights, database rights, data, source code, software, specifications, know how, processes and business methods (in all cases whether registered or unregistered and including all rights to apply for registration) in and relating to this website are owned by or licensed to us. For the purposes of this section, we will call this "our".

You agree that we make our intellectual property available to you for your personal use only. We will allow you to use this intellectual property for your personal, non-commercial use including temporarily printing off one copy, downloading or storing extracts from our website on the condition that you:

  * Comply with the all the terms and conditions of this agreement.
  * Do not copy, alter, modify, reformat, sell, distribute or publish any of the material.
  * Do not create any derivative works.
  * Do not link to any part of our website.
  * Do not print or download any logos, trademarks, service marks or image except as part of the complete web-page of which they form a part.
  * The status of us and our licensors' ownership of all such material is acknowledged in any such printed off, downloaded or stored material.

We will allow you to print off one copy, and download extracts, of any page(s) from our website for your personal non-commercial use only. However if you do this, our status (and that of any identified contributors) as the authors of the material must always be clearly acknowledged.

You retain ownership of all the material you submit or make available on our website. You grant us a perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free, transferable and unlimited licence to use, modify, copy, distribute, publish, transmit such information in any manner and for any purpose but always in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

### OUR LIABILITY

THIS SECTION IS VERY IMPORTANT BECAUSE IT SETS OUT YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES AND OUR LIABILITY TO YOU.

You are responsible for keeping your username, password or other identification secure. If we ask you to complete a registration process when you use our website and this process includes the creation of a username, password and/or other identification information, your username, password and/or other identification information must be kept confidential by you and must not be disclosed to, or shared with, anyone. If you disclose to or share your username, password and/or other identification information with anyone, you are solely responsible for all activities undertaken. If you are concerned that someone may have had access to your username, password and/or other identification information without your permission, please contact us immediately at our address Belgrave House, 76 Buckingham Palace Road, London, SW1W 9TQ , by email at contact@beatthatquote.com.

We are not responsible or liable to you for any loss or damage You may suffer or incur in connection with your failure to keep your username, password or other identification secure.

You are responsible for ensuring any information that you provide us:

  * Is correct complete, accurate and not misleading.
  * Does not infringe anyone's intellectual property rights or privacy rights.
  * Does not violate any law.
  * Is not harmful, fraudulent, defamatory or otherwise offensive.

If you provide feedback on our website or if we ask you to insert information about yourself or circumstances, you are solely responsible for ensuring that all information you provide is correct, complete, accurate and not misleading and that you disclose all relevant facts. We are not responsible or liable to you for any loss or damage you may suffer or incur in connection with your failure to ensure such information is correct and not misleading.

You are responsible for ensuring that any third party that you may wish to contract with has the correct information about you. It is very important that you ensure that all the information held by the third party about you is correct, complete and not misleading and that you have disclosed all relevant facts. It is your responsibility to identify and correct any mistakes or errors in the information, content, material or data held by the third party about you before you obtain any product or service from the third party. Failure to do so could invalidate the product or service provided by the third party and we are not responsible or liable to you for any loss or damage You may suffer or incur in connection with your failure to ensure such information is correct and not misleading.

You are responsible for ensuring that you understand and agree with the terms and conditions of the third party that will be providing the product or service to you before entering into that contract. Our website allows You to apply for a number of products and services. These products and services are all provided by third parties and not us. If you apply for and obtain any product or service, you will be contracting with a third party that will be providing that product or service to you on their own terms and conditions. The application process may involve your clicking on links in either our website or in an email we have sent to you as part of our service to the websites of third parties. These websites are owned by third parties over whom we have no control. Further to that the websites are subject to the third party's privacy policy and terms and conditions. Your access and use of these websites is at your sole risk and it is your responsibility to ensure that you understand and agree with the terms and conditions of the third party whose website you access or use. It is also your responsibility to understand and agree with the terms and conditions which relate to the specific product or service to you before enter into that contract.

You are responsible for making your own enquiries to check that the product or service that you want to apply for is accurate, complete and up-to-date and meets your needs. Our website contains a lot of information and descriptions about the products and services which you may apply for. This information may not provide a complete description of all the features, terms and conditions applicable to those products. Further much of the information is provided by third party product or service providers and we do not monitor, verify or endorse the information and it may be inaccurate, incomplete or out of date. Although we use reasonable endeavours to ensure that the information on our website is reliable and try to correct any errors or omissions as soon as practicable after being made aware of them, you should check that such information is accurate, complete and up to date. 

You are responsible for ensuring that you have appropriate virus checking software on your computer. We cannot guarantee that our website is uncorrupted or free from viruses which may harm your computer and are not responsible or liable to you for any loss or damage you may suffer in this regard where caused by any third party.

We do not seek to exclude or limit any liability that cannot be limited or excluded under any applicable law. This includes our liability for things such as fraud, death or personal injury caused by negligence and also the responsibilities we have under certain legislation such as the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000.

We will not be liable to you for any loss of income, revenue, business, profits or contract, anticipated savings, data, goodwill or opportunity, direct, indirect or consequential loss or damage incurred by you in connection with any access, use, or inability to access or use our website where:

  * You have not complied with any part of these terms and conditions.
  * We are not in breach of a legal duty of care owed to you by us or by any of our employees or agents, or
  * the loss or damage you suffered by our breach of these terms and conditions was not reasonably foreseeable, or
  * the damage or loss was caused by events outside our control; or
  * to the extent that you have contributed to your loss or damage by failing to act reasonably in the circumstances or by failing to take reasonable steps to mitigate your loss or damage.

### YOUR LIABILITY

If you use our website, it is reasonable for us to expect that you will adhere to these terms and conditions. If we think you have breached any of these terms and conditions or demonstrated inappropriate conduct when using our website, we may take measures to terminate or suspend your access to the website.

If your use of our website causes us to suffer any loss or damage, you will be responsible for reimbursing us for any such loss or damage that we may suffer.

### CUSTOMER SERVICE, COMPLAINTS AND CONTACTING US

Our aim is to at all times provide you with an excellent service. However, if you are unhappy with our service for any reason, please contact our customer services team (Complaints Handling) at our address Belgrave House, 76 Buckingham Palace Road, London, SW1W 9TQ or by submitting a complaint.

We will endeavour to acknowledge receipt of your complaint, in writing, within five business days and we will inform you of the name or job title of the individual handling the complaint. We may combine the acknowledgement of the complaint with our final response, but in any event we aim to resolve complaints at the earliest opportunity.

If you are unhappy with any product or service that you have been introduced to through our website, we recommend that you approach the provider of that product or service directly. If you require any provider's contact details, please contact our customer services team who will be happy to assist.

### INFORMATION ABOUT SPECIFIC PRODUCTS OR SERVICES ON OUR WEBSITE

The following sections form part of the terms and conditions and provide more specific guidance on certain products and services.

#### Insurance products

We are regulated by the Financial Services Authority.

In this respect, we are an appointed representative of Best Value Financial Services Limited that is authorised and regulated by the Financial Services Authority. 

Our Insurance Service

Our insurance service allows you to compare providers for a range of insurance products. You will need to answer a number of questions on our website in order for the product providers to provide you accurate quotations for the product(s) you are interested in. In this respect it is very important that you answer all the questions asked accurately and truthfully because we and the insurance product providers' results we show to you will rely on your answers. If you are in any doubt as to whether any information is relevant you should disclose it. If you do not provide all such information your selected insurer may be able to treat your insurance policy as void (as if it never existed). With respect to our life insurance product, this service is different as it allows you to be contacted by a specialist who may be able to assist you further with your enquiry.

If you complete an enquiry form for an insurance product on our website we will conduct a search for policies and will display the results on the screen. To assist you in completing the enquiry form, we may provide defaulted answers to some questions, and in other instances obtain certain information from third parties (such as motor vehicle data and address details). Please ensure that this information is complete and accurate, and change it if necessary. We will also email you details of the quotes you have obtained from Our system with appropriate links to allow you to purchase an insurance policy.

Insurers and brokers on our panel may use the information you supply in the enquiry form to carry out credit checks through licensed credit-referencing agencies. This forms part of their underwriting process which determines your eligibility for a quote. A copy of such searches will be held on your credit record. We do not carry out any such credit searches nor do we have any access to this information.

Insurers and brokers also subscribe to industry databases to check the information provided in your enquiry form to reduce incidences of fraud. They may therefore search these databases before providing you with an insurance quotation. We do not have access to these databases.

If you have agreed to receive newsletters and marketing material from us, the information you supply on your original enquiry form may be used by us to produce further indicative quotations for you (typically approximately one month before the anniversary of your original cover start date). In order for us to do this the insurers and brokers may carry out checks of the same type as those described above. Please let us know by contacting contact@beatthatquote.com if you do not want us to do this or alternatively unsubscribe from receiving newsletters and marketing material from us.

You are also able to save your details on our system and use these as the basis for making amended or new quotation requests in future.

If you choose to purchase an insurance policy following completion of an enquiry form on our website, we remind you again of your responsibilities (as set out above) to ensure the insurance product provider has the correct information about you and that you understand that you agree with the terms and conditions of that insurance product provider including the restrictions, exclusions and conditions of that policy. You may also be contacted by product providers whose prices are displayed in your results, who may be able to provide alternative quotes that are not available online.

### OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We take the protection of your personal data very seriously. This section explains what information we collect from you, what we do with it, how we keep it secure and the circumstances upon which we provide it to third parties. If you have any questions, comments or requests regarding this Privacy Policy please contact our customer services Team at our address Belgrave House, 76 Buckingham Palace Road, London, SW1W 9TQ or via email at contact@beatthatquote.com.

By using this site, you are giving us permission to use the data you provide us in the ways set out in this privacy policy.

Information that we collect from you:

To take advantage of some of the services we offer, you might be required to provide us with certain information about yourself. This may include doing things such as registering your contact details or completing certain forms on our website. You may also be asked to provide us with information about yourself if you wish to participate in any discussion forums, enter any contest or competition on our website or if you choose to contact us for any reason. We also collect details of your visit to our website and your use of it.

Sensitive personal data:

The nature of our business is such that we may also on occasion ask you to provide sensitive personal data as defined in the Data Protection Act 1998 (for example, questions relating to criminal convictions for the purpose of providing car insurance quotations). By proceeding with obtaining a quote, we will take that as your explicit consent to such information being processed by ourselves and the relevant third party product providers.

Use of cookies:

We may also collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type using a cookie file which is stored in the hard drive of your computer. Cookies help us to improve our website and deliver a better and more personalised service to you. They enable us to:

  * personalise your experience on our website, speed up your searches and help us select services or materials for inclusion on the website which may be of interest to you;
  * monitor general traffic patterns and usage of our website to help us to improve our website design and lay out.

Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance. If you choose not to receive cookies, you may not be able to use certain features of our website.

How will we use your data?

We (or third parties acting on our behalf) may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * to provide you with the information, products or services that you request from us and/or
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service when you choose to do so; and/or
  * to contact you by letter, telephone or e-mail to inform you about other products and services which may be of interest to you; and/or
  * notify you of our news, changes to the website, special events or other services we think may interest you.

We will also disclose your personal information to third parties who provide the products and services that you have enquired about via our website.

We also may need to disclose your personal information where it is necessary to comply with any applicable laws or to protect ourselves or our users (including exchanging information with other companies for the purposes of fraud protection), or in the event that we sell our business, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective buyer of our business.

How do we store your personal information and keep it secure?

As required by the Data Protection Act 1998, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of personal information which you have provided via this website, to prevent unauthorised access. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure your personal details remain secure. The personal information that we collect from you may also be transferred to and stored outside of the European Economic Area.

Your Rights:

If you do not agree to the privacy policy then you should not enter any of your personal information on our website.

If at any time after you have provided personal information to us and you want to object to your personal data being used by us, you need to let us know by either contacting our customer services team at our address Belgrave House, 76 Buckingham Palace Road, London, SW1W 9TQ, or by sending an email to us at [unsubscribe@beatthatquote.com](mailto:unsubscribe@beatthatquote.com). We will endeavour to process your request as soon as possible, but in some cases it may take us up to 28 days to process your request.

You may request a copy of the information we hold about you. We will be happy to provide you with such information upon request and the payment of £10 in order to cover our administrative expenses in relation to your request.

Our privacy policy applies solely to information collected by us through our website. Please note that we are not responsible for what any third party content provider or other third party offering goods and services via websites or linked to or framed around our website may do with any personal information that you may provide them. Accordingly, please ensure that you also read their data protection and privacy terms and conditions very carefully before providing them with your personal information.

### MISCELLANEOUS

Any failure on our part to enforce any right will not constitute a waiver of such rights.

These terms and conditions replace any previous terms and conditions regarding the use of our website.

These terms and conditions are subject to English law and the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts.

### QUESTIONS?

If you have any questions about these terms and conditions or have a general query about the services that we provide, please get in touch. You can find our contact details by clicking on this link: Contact us.

Thank you for visiting our website!
